



<u>piyush.jain0271@gmail.com</u> Linkedin



8005636360



Vaishali Nagar, Jaipur

SKILLS

Angular

PHP

Node.JS/Express.JS (Basic)

MongoDB (Basic)

SocialEngine (CRM)

SOL

DBMS

JavaScript

JQuerv

Ajax

Bootstrap
HTML/CSS

Git/GitHub/BitBucket

Rest/Soap Api's

LANGUAGES

English

Professional Working Proficiency

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

INTEREST

Reading Blogs and Articles

World Geopolitics

Watching movies

Piyush Jain

Software Developer

Adaptable professional with 3.5+ years of experience and a proven knowledge of application development. Aiming to leverage my skills to successfully fill the software engineer role at your company. I have always had a natural ability for working with numbers and breaking down complex problems into smaller component parts.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer BigStep Technologies

06/2019 - Present, Gurgaon/India

A Few Projects

ImpactGroup

- Description This Project is developed by using Angular and Php, client want us to make a
 platform where users can join Groups and on each group user can post any text, images or
 video feeds and create polls, events and many more, something similar to Facebook.
- Role My work is to get requirement from client and then make time estimations and break whole work in smaller pieces and created this project on Angular and PHP as Fullstack developer.
- Technologies Angular, SQL, PHP, SocialEngine (SocialEngine is an CRM, based on zend and php which follows MVC structure) and other integrations.

SoFood

- Description This Project is an ecommerce site, where users can make online payments
 and buy products online from any store, Here I have create an ecommerce website and
 implemented PayPal payment system and Integrated DHL Api's for delivery services and
 many more other tasks as well.
- Role Worked as an Fullstack Developer.
- Technologies Angular, SQL, PHP, SocialEngine and other integrations

LitFuel

- Description This Project is an event based site. Where users can create events and book them
- Role Worked as an backend developer
- Technologies HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery, Ajax, SQL, PHP, SocialEngine and other integrations.

SiteBooking

- Description This Project is an plugin and a BigStep product. where users can create/start
 any services and users can book them
- Role Worked as an backend developer.
- Technologies HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery, Ajax, SQL, PHP, SocialEngine and other integrations.

INTERNSHIP

Internship in MEAN stack

You start technologies · Internship May 2018 - Jul 2018, Jaipur Area, India

CERTIFICATES

Mean Stack (Udemy)

Responsive Web Design (FreeCodeCamp)

BigStep Appriciations

Client's Appriciations

EDUCATION

Bachelor Of Technology

Swami Keshwanand Institute Of Technology

04/2015 - 04/2019, Jaipur/India

Courses

• Computer Science and Engineering

Intermediate

St. Austin Senior Secondary School

2014 - 2015, Jodhpur/India

Courses

Science with Mathematics and physics (PCM)